Next, I will introduce you to the production of our Yang Gaolong.
As I introduced earlier, my name is Niko.
Today we are mainly talking about the production of Yang Gaolong.
In our Karo, there are already some pre-set Yang Gaolong fabrics.
You can see these Yang Gaolong fabrics from these color balls.
Some of them are made of wool, and some of them are made of
So we have about 11 pieces of Yang Gaolong fabric in our basket. You can use it directly. You can see these effects.
Next, let's open our Karo software.
Then I opened a clothing document for him.
Then here I opened a clothing document and applied the Yang Gaolong fabric in our basket to it.
We can put the mouse here.
You can take a look at the Yang Gaolong fabric.
This is the effect of the Yang Gaolong.
Here we choose to apply a piece of Yang Gaolong fabric to it.
After application, you may feel a little confused because there is no effect of Yang Gaolong on it.
This is because whether it is made of wool or made of clay, the Yang Gaolong needs to be shown in the window to see it.
Then I want to ask if there is any material.
When you play back, you may see that you are presented with materials.
Then we show a look at the effect at the same time.
I can see it.
There is nothing to follow.
What is the effect?
Then we click on the fabric, we can see the properties below, it has a hair growth effect.
Now we apply another piece of hair growth to it.
Similarly, we synchronize to see its effect.
After synchronization, you can see another hair growth effect.
Now we click on the fabric, we can see the properties below, it has a hair growth effect.
After synchronization, you can see the properties below, it has a hair growth effect.
It is a gray map that can truly show the O2 structure of the object.
The black in the picture represents the flat area, and the white area represents the highest or the most convex area.
Its production method is to be done in PS.
It needs to be discolored in PS and then adjusted to the color.
Finally, it is high-gloss and blurred.
Then you can apply it to the simulation map.
Adjusting the settings is to make the black and white contrast more obvious.
High-gloss and blurred are mainly to make the transition more natural.
You can also see that there are some parameter settings below the simulation map.
For example, the degree of simulation, the height of the line, the particle diameter, and so on.
Let's take a closer look at these parameters.
First, you look at the original picture of its simulation group and a picture after high-gloss and blurred.
When you do the simulation later, don't forget to do high-gloss and blurred.
First, let's take a look at the degree of simulation.
The higher the degree of simulation, the higher the white area is.
Let's look at the movement.
If the movement is positive, it will float.
If the movement is negative, it will line up.
This is a very simple example.
Next, the height of the simulation.
The height is equal to 0.5.
The increase and decrease in the height of the simulation will decrease.
The result is another example like this.
When the particle diameter is one, the edge will be smoother.
The next thing is the continuity of the simulation.
The consistency of the simulation is to unlock the gap.
This is the meaning of the parameter of our
Next, we can also see a black gap in the window of the synchronization column.
This is caused by technical reasons.
It is mainly caused by the gap between the picture and the costume.
There are two ways to solve it.
One is to adjust the parameters of the synchronization picture.
Then I will make it a little bigger here.
Then you can synchronize and see the effect.
Then you will find that the black gap in the front will be smaller.
But other high-end dragon effects
There will be cracks
So you need to adjust the movement value repeatedly to make it a suitable degree.
Then we synchronize here to see the effect.
You can see that there is still a little black gap in the front.
Because sometimes the movement value can not completely eliminate the black gap.
If you don't recommend this kind of black gap, you can use the synchronization picture to do it.
If you recommend it, you can use the hair to show the high-end dragon.
You can also see that our shoulder line also has a black gap.
Then we synchronize it.
This is a piece of black gap.
Here we use another way to adjust the black gap between the shoulder line and the collar here.
We can choose its sewing line
Adjust the angle of the sewing line to 360 degrees.
Mainly bend it.
Then the sewing line in the collar here.
We also choose it
Then adjust it to 360 degrees
Simulate
Then you can see it
The place where it is placed will be wrapped in
Let's look at the results in parallel
Let's zoom in a little bit
I may have been too far away just now
You can clearly see
The black gap in its gap
The gap has been eliminated
Let's sum up here
If you have an image of the illusion
Showed a sun-dry dragon
If there is a problem with the black gap
It can be solved in two ways
One is to adjust the moving value of the illusion picture
The other is to adjust the angle of the
Then everyone adjusts the moving value of the illusion picture
Need to try repeatedly
To find a suitable value
Make it look more suitable
The same here
Because there is a pocket on my front
Then I applied a default mask to it
In order to make everyone see it more clearly
I change it to a blue
Simulate at the same time
Then everyone can see
Your pocket
Some of them have been penetrated by the sun-dry dragon
How to solve this problem
Here I will give you a concept
A concept called the default image
The default image
The default image mainly refers to
A hair effect with different length, thickness and density on a board
It is a gray image like this
Then the black part does not grow hair
Then the white part
It is an effect of growing hair
Gray is in the middle of black and white
If you don't want it to grow hair in this pocket
Then you can fill in the board here
Fill in black
Then wait a minute
Let's do this default image
Maybe the digging will be faster
But some customers
Or your board master
Is not allowed to cut the board
So you can do it in the way I said
Then we have to do the default image of the simulation
We have to put it in the window of the flower arrangement
Then
Make a simple arrangement for its board
Then we will pour it out
When pouring out
Then what you need to pay attention to here
Is that its size is 1 to 1
Then the resolution is 300
Then the selection
Here you need to select its basic line or internal line
Then keep it out
Then we give it a name
Give it a picture
Give it a name
No card
Really card
I think it's black
Then
What we are going to make is one of our
The default image of the simulation picture
Then you pour it out
After that
Open it in the PS
Then this one to one
Give it a picture of the board
Open it
After opening it
Here I may not have lined up well just now
Then everyone can do it later
Line it up closely
What we need to do now
Use the simulation tool
Put this pocket
Where it is covered
Select it
Add a layer to it
And fill it with black
Because the black one
I also introduced it before
The black one
The place is not thin
After filling it
We used the original
A Yang Gaorong of the simulation picture
So we need to
The simulation picture
Also give it
Open in the PS
So you have to find this first
A position of the simulation picture
Give it a position
Close it out
Then
On your computer
Keep it out
Then we keep it
In its own folder
Position
Right
This one is used in the PS
Then
Open this one
The simulation picture
In the PS
Open
After opening it
What we need to do
One job is to check it
A resolution
Take a look
The resolution of this simulation picture
With your one-to-one board
Is the resolution of the picture consistent
If so
You can directly change it
The simulation picture
Define as a pattern
If it is not consistent
Then you need to adjust
Its resolution
After defining the pattern
You are in the board picture
Give it a new layer
Then fill in
The pattern you just defined
After filling it
You need to change the position
When the black one
Fill it out
Then
Make it into a picture
You don't have to worry about
That part of the card just now
After that part of the card
There will be a playback
Then
Now
Take a look at the back first
After that
We are in the cloud
The text here
Delete it in the original text
Then
Open it
Apply it to it
The texture you just kept out
Maybe the picture is a bit big
So there's a little bit of a card here
You can see
What we just did
The picture has been uploaded
Next
What we need to do
In one of the windows of the print
Put it in front of it
The position of the pocket
Give it to it
In the black area
After that
We can
In our
Under the simulation mode
Add it to the simulation picture
What is the simulation picture
Is what you just did
The picture you just made
Because there is a memory function in the cloud software
If you are the same picture
Before that
After the position has been adjusted
After that
No need to adjust anymore
So here
You still need to set it
Simulation degree
Move
And its particle diameter
If you can't remember
You can apply this piece of fabric in the library
Come up
Take a look at its parameter settings
You may have
After using the simulation picture
There is no adjustment
A parameter below
That means
Your simulation picture
May not have any effect at all
Here
We come again
Comprehensively
See the effect
OK
Then
Now
Comprehensively
After that
We can see
Its pocket
It won't be pierced by the high-heels
Now
I'll give you a summary
How to do the default picture of the simulation picture
First
In the hard drive mode
One by one
Draw a board
Then pay attention to a setting of parameters
The second
Is in the PS
Select the part that is blocked
Fill it with black
Then
In the PS
Open its simulation picture to it
Then you need to check
Is the pixel of the simulation picture and the board picture consistent
If so
You can
The simulation picture is defined as a pattern
If it is not consistent
Then you need to adjust its pixel
Then
Finally
In the one-to-one board layer
A new layer is created
Fill in the pattern you defined
And adjust its layer sequence
Then
Finally
It's a picture of the jpg
Then
This is our
The effect of a default picture of the simulation picture
Mainly
When you use the simulation picture to make a high-density solution
There is a penetration problem
You can use this method
Then
Let's take a look at its
Cutting line problem
Then
Let's take a look at its cutting line at the same time
Let's take a look at its cutting line
Then you can see that its cutting line is not very obvious
Here we can use the simulation method to solve it
Mainly to adjust some parameters for the simulation
Here
Here, I adjusted its frame first
And then I adjusted the beginning of the star
And in order to make it more clear to everyone, I changed it to black
Because the white one may not be very clear to you
The point is that you need to open the 3D
After opening the 3D, it will have a cut shadow mark
Then you can adjust the strength of the line drawing to make it a little bigger
At the same time, you need to adjust the distance between the Z-axis of the bright line
The main thing is to adjust the distance between the Z-axis of the bright line
You can let the bright line float
Because it is the Yang-Gaorong shown by the line drawing
So the line drawing has a degree of change
If you don't adjust the distance between the Z-axis of the bright line
Then it will fall in
OK, let's watch the same line
Then you can see the distance between the Z-axis on my adjustment is too big
You can adjust it again
A little bit smaller
Then look at the back of the head
What if you have made a sticker after that
On the hair
Or add a sticker on the calligraphy
If you can't see it after the back of the head
It's possible that your sticker has been blocked
You can also choose a heavy sticker
Then adjust the distance between his sentences
Then you can see his obvious trace of a cut
This is a way to express the cut with a name line
OK
Because this is more like your line
So when you are making Yang Gaolong
Be very patient
OK
This is expressed in the way of the name line
The other one
We are doing it in another way
Here is mainly to choose this kind of cut
Then add the internal line to it
Then the point to pay attention to here is
Add an internal line to the top and bottom
Then let's adjust the angle of this internal line
Will the hair be added at the back?
Because what I am introducing to you now is an effect of using a calligraphy to show Yang Gaolong
What about the back?
I will introduce to you the effect of hair growth to show Yang Gaolong
You can see that my current angle is set in the opposite way
So here I will change his angle again
Then the angle here is based on my effect
Refer to the settings
Then everyone after that
When setting the angle
You can do a setting according to the effect you want
OK
Then we are the same
Let's take a look at the effect
Then you can see his one cut line mark
This method is mainly made with the internal line
Then set the angle of the inner line of a fold line
Set up the initial angle and the final angle
Then we have a situation to set up the natural angle
Look at the angle of the front
Also set the angle of the back
Then set the total angle of the front
The whole angle of the front
And the length of the front
Then I will summarize it for everyone
We do the line cut
There are two ways to cut the thread, one is to use the folk thread method, and then you need to adjust some parameters of the folk thread, which mainly refers to the need to open its 3D to adjust the strength of its hair line, and then you can adjust some other parameters of the folk thread to make it look more folk.
Another way is that you can add an inner thread to the top and bottom of it, and then set its folding angle, which can also show a trace of its cut.
The above is a method and technique for us to show the hair of the sheep with the phantom picture.
The next thing I want to introduce to you is the method of showing the sheep with hair.
From these three materials, you can see how the result is.
These materials are wool
Next, let me show you an illustration of a material ball channels.
We can apply a piece of fabric to it and then look at it here
We also changed its picture size a little bit before the rendering
Then synchronize the rendering to see the effect
Now you can see the effect of our Yang Gaorong
Here we can look at one of its parameters is hair
The main thing is to express the effect of Yang Gaorong with hair
The main thing to pay attention to here is its bending strength
You can see that its bending strength is very small
This is a state of zero
Then let's take a look at its default picture
We also introduced the concept of default picture in the previous video
Then we open a conversion of the default picture
That is to change the size of this default picture
Then we synchronize to take a look
Then we will see another Yang Gaorong effect
If you don't have a ready-made Yang Gaorong fabric
Then you can use the conversion of Yang Gaorong in the library
Then adjust their size
You can get the effect of the Yang Gaorong you want
Here I adjust the size again
You can see the effect
You can see that you can also combine hair
And some other parameters of hair
To adjust it
Let you have a better Yang Gaorong effect
Here I slightly adjusted its bending strength
Then the Yang Gaorong effect it comes out
It will be softer
And I adjusted its thickness
Here because I am a plate
So my thickness is adjusted to 1.5 mm
If you are making clothes
It's more complicated
Or in a particularly complex style
I suggest that the thickness of the hair
Don't exceed 1 mm
Then adjust the length of the hair
You can take a look
Now is another effect
Here we will change the length of its default picture
Size to change it
Put the area that is growth
Can be adjusted with the hair
In addition to thekur business
Take a look at the
The result of the Yang Gaorong made with hair
We talked about it
In terms of methods
Okay, let's use hair to make Yang Gaolong, first of all, you need to pay attention to two points, one is that the bending strength of the hair is small, and the bending strength of the hair mainly refers to the bending strength of a hair.
If your straight is larger, it will be smaller and larger, and the bending will be more obvious, so the bending strength of the hair to show Yang Gaolong must be small.
The second point is to apply the
default image to the default image. The default image is the black area that we introduced earlier. The white area is thin, and the gray area is in the middle, and you can see that its default image has length, thickness, and density, and then you can see the hair on the sofa, and you can see that this default image is applied, and you can see such an effect.
Next, I have a
costume to apply a Yang Gaolong fabric to it.
That same
way, we apply a piece of Yang Gaolong fabric to it.
Yes, it takes a lot of patience to make this Yang Gaolong, because its effect is shown through the synchronization column.
Then, we apply one fabric to its door shavings and the material here.
And then we apply another fabric to it.
Then let's apply a fabric to it
And then we give him the door and pocket for him to apply nylon matte fabric
And then his lining, we apply the fabric of Dylan Sedin
So you can take a look at what we have now
It's all a Chinese interface
And then we adjust the color for him
Change the color here as well
And then after we're done, we're going to apply it and then we're going to show it to him
So before we show it to you, we're going to take a look at it because we're going to use hair to show the woolen hair
The hair is usually used in the key position
For example, the back of this costume is actually without hair
In this case, you can adjust its back and its side material type to give it a plant-like effect
So that way, you're not too slow and you're not going to let your computer hurt your computer
And here we're going to do a synchronization and we're going to take a look at the results
And then after synchronization, you can see that his collar and his body is not that loose
And then I'm going to introduce it to you
If you want to make your high-heeled dragon or you want to make your high-heeled dragon a little looser
So here we're going to take a look at how we're going to loosen the collar because the collar is a custom layer so you're going to take his custom
I'm going to delete his original sewing line and then I'm going to sew another sewing line for him
So here's the sewing line type that doesn't need to be changed
I'm going to change the sewing line type to the same collar and I'm going to sew it on the side of the collar
So here we don't need to change his sewing line type
So the purpose of doing this is mainly to tie it up
And then we can know that after we've switched it to the texture surface, you can see that the black one is the back of the fabric so you need to turn it over
Let his front face out
So then after that you can set its folding angle so here I set 260 degrees and then the folding intensity also adjusted to be closer to the angle I set and then the simulation
So you can take a look at that it's not as tight as I want it to be
And then what do we want to make it look more evident
Select it on the outer contour line in the circle.
Give it an inner line.
Then you can adjust the diameter here yourself.
The inner line here needs to be extended and cancelled.
Because it's a symmetrical board.
If you hook it up, it will appear.
Two inner lines.
Let's set the angle as well.
The angle here is 90 degrees.
90 degrees is the state in which your front will protrude.
Then you can see that your current collar has a slightly looser feeling.
Let's look at the results at the same time.
OK, then everyone takes a look.
Then you can see that your collar is slightly looser.
But the front of his collar feels like a large dragon's tail.
If you want to make him.
A little looser.
Here you can increase the thickness of his collision.
The thickness of the collision.
Mainly refers to the vacuum between the board and the board.
He can't see it.
So you can also let his board.
Give him a little looser.
Similarly, we can do it at the same time.
Then you can see that the current collar is already looser.
This is a looser way of the collar.
Then let's take a look at the looser way of our big body.
Then we take a look at the looser way of our big body.
How much can I take by already.
It's a looser way of the collar.
The first one is to adjust the thickness of a material.
What if the thickness of the material is thicker?
Relative singers hair will be stronger and more enduring.
The effect
Let's take a look at the results at the same time
OK, so this is a way to adjust the thickness of the fabric
In addition, we can also choose to adjust the conflict thickness of these panels in the same way
Make it a little bit loose
You need to simulate it after you've adjusted it
OK
We
Let's simulate it again
So this is a wave pattern
And you can see that the hands on the fabric are not veryенный
But, the
The
I
Can
Control
It
For
The
Pattern
And
You can
Like
Write
Your
Design
As
You
Eat
Your
Food
For
Your
Business
You can see that the current effect is more loose than before, and the feeling is more thick.
Next, we can see that the bottom edge is also flat.
Here you can choose its sewing line.
Then change its sewing line type to flat sewing.
You can also take a look at the same thing.
Then we synchronize and take a look at the effect.
Then you can see that the bottom edge of its clothing has been loosened.
Then I will summarize some of the methods of loosening.
The neck part can be adjusted to the angle of the sewing line, the inner line of the sewing line, and the angle of the setting.
The upper part mainly sets the thickness of the hemline and the thickness of the hemline.
Of course, the thickness of the fabric can also be set.
In addition, you can see that your pocket is blocked by the fur when hemline.
Here we also need to make a default picture.
The method of default picture.
The method is the same as the one we introduced earlier.
In the pattern, let it simply line up and then give it a 1 to 1 quick photo.
After the quick photo is done, you can save a name for it.
OK, then we save it.
Save it.
After saving it, we also need to save its default picture, which is a default picture in the default picture.
Switch to the front.
OK, save it.
You also look at its width and height.
Because I made it with a default picture in the library.
So I adjusted its size.
If you want to adjust its size later,
When you open it with PS,
Be sure to adjust its size as well.
Then I'll turn these two off for him first.
Then I use PS to get the 1 to 1 version of the picture I just poured out.
That is, the cherry blossom layout.
Open it for him.
Here, you also need to select the areas that are blocked.
For example, his two pockets are blocked.
Then you need to select these two areas.
Then give him a new layer and fill it in black.
Because black is not hairy.
Remember that black is not hairy.
The same as his replacement picture can also be added to him.
The first step is to check its resolution.
Check the two resolution.
After checking,
We remember that we just have a replacement picture.
Adjust its size, right?
Then you need to be in the PS.
The same as its size,
Also make changes.
Yes, black is not hairy.
What do you use to change the size of the picture.
Then we're going to do this again.
Then make a black,
Then we fill the blank.
Then we make a new one here.
Then I want to change the size of the picture.
If I can fit the size correctly,
It's very easy.
That's how it works.
Then I'll do it again.
Then I'll do this again.
Then I'm going to change the size of this picture.
Make a new layer here.
I've already demonstrated the function twice
You should watch the live broadcast
You should have learned
A way to do the default chart
Let's save it
Then
Switch it to
A simulated state
Then
Let's apply it here in the text
Just now
Flower pattern
Then
The purpose of this step
Mainly to locate
Because if you say
The black area is not in the correct position
It will be
You know
After that
You apply this cherry blossom layout to it
Just go to the default chart
Then you give it
On the application of its original texture
If you say you have texture
Then you apply it to it
Because I don't use texture here
Directly made of fur
Then we synchronize
Then you can see your pocket
It's already out
Not penetrated by fur
This is a
For some parts
The problem of being penetrated by fur
It's possible that everyone will see
Your texture is penetrated by fur
Right
The same
We synchronize
Look at the effect
Does the texture penetrate the hair
Then
We can see
Its texture is not penetrated by hair, right?
Then this is because
When we set the hair
For its back
The material used is a plant sun
An effect
Did not set hair for it
Then if you say
In the later stage
And after setting
You don't want it
Just grow a little bit of hair
Or say it grows shorter
Then you can also apply it to the default chart
Ah
That's it
Then this is above
This is us
Use hair to make
One of the techniques of Yang Gaolong
And some of the problems you encounter
Then
What's next
We'll give him this costume
Make him some outfits
Then
After you wear it
Is everyone
On the poster
An effect picture
Then today
We give you
Yang Gaolong
Mainly use two methods to make Yang Gaolong
One is to change the picture
The other is
The effect of hair
First of all, you have to understand
The meaning of the change picture
And its parameter settings
Then the other one is
If you use the change picture
When the hair shows Yang Gaolong
It will come out
The black gap
How do you solve it
And a problem with the pocket
There are also cutting lines
problem
And a loose problem
Today
I mainly talked about these
I hope everyone can understand
Because if you make Yang Gaolong
Maybe everyone needs to be a little patient
Because of its every adjustment
All need to be in the window
Out of the window
Then
Let's add it to the configuration
Let's take a look at the final effect
Let's close the Eugene
Let's see we can just
On the net
Pressure, usually we are here to make a down jacket, so in general, it is not necessary to use pressure to show it.
Then everyone pays attention, you must pay attention to one of the settings of the scroll engine when you scroll.
For example, its scroll engine is to choose the GPU or CPU, if your computer is good enough.
Here we usually use the CPU when scrolling these blind spots.
Then everyone here also needs to pay attention to its focus value and the setting of the longest scroll time.
The most important thing is the quality of the light source and the material here.
You have to adjust to the highest one.
If you adjust to the light color of the hair, because if you set the thickness of your hair to be a little bigger,
The hair will have shadows and it will look gray and dirty.
At this time, you can adjust its light source and material to the highest and give it a light effect.
Then you can see that there is a row of lights on the right side of the scroll window.
Then you can combine the effect of these lights to show its final effect.
The hair is gray because the hair is not lighted.
The light on the hair will have a shadow and it will look gray.
If you don't want it to look gray, you can put a light on it in front of it.
For example, a paper light can also be used.
Then you can adjust the brightness of the light source and material to the highest and the lowest.
Then you also have to adjust the focus value to a little lower.
The longest rendering time is usually 20 minutes.
Then you can set it a little longer.
Because usually the rendering of hair needs a long time.
There is no card, it is now synchronized rendering.
You can take a look at the rendering effect.
The effect is getting better and better.
There is no card.
Because the rendering of this kind of hair will be very slow.
So our Yang Gaorong live broadcast today is here.
If you have any questions, you can tell me on the live broadcast.
Then I will answer everyone.